Felipe Reis

<u>falreis.eng.br</u> <u>github.com/falreis</u> <u>linkedin.com/in/falreis</u>

A full-stack software developer for web and desktop environments since 2006. Extensive experience working on large-scale projects in accounting, education, and finance industries. Highly proficient in ASP.NET C#, PHP, and relational databases. I'm specializing in computer vision (segmentation, classification and image detection; edge detection), using deep learning.

Technical Skills

Languages: ASP.NET C#/VB, C++, Java, PHP, JavaScript, HTML, Python

Databases: Oracle, MySQL, PostgreSQL, MSSQL

Frameworks/Libraries: jQuery, Bootstrap, Visual Studio, Eclipse

Other: Scrum, Git/GitHub, SVN, Google Cloud, Amazon AWS, Anaconda, Jupyter, GIMP

Work Experience

IFMG - Campus Formiga - Temporary Professor

Formiga, Brazil | July 2020 - current

- Teaching subjects in the Computer Science course;
- Subjects: Artificial Intelligence, Operational Research, Numerical Analysis, Discrete Mathematics, Classic Computer Problems (Machine Learning).

Reis Eng. e Software Ltda. - Freelancer Developer

Belo Horizonte, Brazil | January 2018 - current*

- Development of web, desktop and computer vision applications.
- Technologies used: ASP.NET C# 4.7, Angular, Python, Tensorflow, PHP (Wordpress).

Prodabel - Information Technology Analyst

Belo Horizonte, Brazil | May 2014 - July 2017

- Gathered and analyzed requirements to define solutions, developed and supported new accounting software, CASP a Brazilian standard for public accounting;
- Migrated an old accounting software to the new version (including data), developed procedures for accounting processing/closure, developed reports, allowing publish the balance sheet based on the system's data.
- Technologies used: PowerBuilder 12.5 (Desktop), PHP Zend 1.1 (Web), Oracle (Database)

<u>Ci&T Software S.A.</u> - Full Software Engineer

Belo Horizonte, Brazil | July 2013 - March 2014

- Developed and supported an educational software (academic and financial areas);
- Technologies used: Classic ASP (Web), Oracle (Database)

<u>CSI Services Ltda.</u> - System Information Developer

Belo Horizonte, Brazil | September 2012 - June 2013

- Gathered and analyzed requirements, created Scrum Backlog, defined system architecture and developed new software to manage company's printers and hardware resources (outsourced company);
- Technologies used: ASP.NET C# 4.0 + NHibernate (Web), MSSQL (Database), C++ (CUPS)

Education

PUC Minas, Brazil - Masters in Informatics	December 2020
Udacity - Self Driving Car Engineer Nanodegree Program	May 2018
PUC Minas, Brazil - Industrial Engineering, Lato sensu post graduation	October 2017
CEFET-MG, Brazil - Computer Engineering, B.S.	December 2012
CEFET-MG, Brazil - Industrial Computer, Technical Level	December 2005

Other Information

Language Skills - Portuguese (native), English (proficient), French (intermediary proficiency) **Scientific Research -** 5 papers, published in conferences and magazines **Detailed information and work experiences before 2012** - please visit my <u>LinkedIn</u> profile.